# Joejo Si Qi Zhou

zmqjoe@hotmail.com www.linkedin.com/in/joejo-zhou https://github.com/Learningitnow (416)721-8932 Toronto, On, Canada

#### **Profile**

A highly punctual and outgoing junior front-end web developer leveraging hard yet fun casino working background to build a more friendly, interactive user first experience on the web. Recently earned a certificate in full stack development from UofT coding Bootcamp, with newly developed skills in JavaScript, Node, React.js, and responsive web design to solve real world projects and applications.

## Experience

#### Coding Boot Camper, University of Toronto -Sept 2020 - now

 Eager to learn, Attending class every day. Excited to emerging the learning new material everyday.

### Table game dealer, Casino woodbine — May 2019 - Now

- Opened game at assigned table, counted contents, verified count with closing list under supervisor, inspected playing cards.
- Exchanged paper currency to playing cheques
- Maintain continuous security of assigned game at all times
- Notify supervisor of any suspicious or unusual activity and/or transactions in a timely and responsible manner
- Maintained the honesty and integrity both on and off game tables
- Accurate and immediate calculations of payouts as established by the rules and procedures
  of a specific game.

#### Rosesun window blinds-install and sale — AUG 2017 - MAY 2019

- Communicated with clients in daily basis and provided accurate advice
- Performed installing windows covering on various environment, bot commercial and residential unit
- Fabricated window blinds and repairs on both motorized and non motorized products
- Well knowledge on operating scissor lift and assembly scaffolding; developed well knowledge
  of the various type of products, such as motorized, regular, specialized blinds
- Handled large amount of currency form customer to employer on daily basis
- Operated precision measuring instrument and electronic test device
- Maintained company, warehouse, equipment and inventory; followed routine maintenance check list; reported duty everyday to superior

## Education

University of Toronto SCS — Full Stack Web Development 2020 University of Toronto — Management Studies 2008

# Web devoleop Skills

JavaScript / Node.JS / MySQL / MVC / Express / Bootstrap / HTML / CSS /